# from https://opentdb.com/api_config.php
question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Is a dog a mammal?",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "French is an official language in Canada.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }
]

